

# **CONTACT ME**

- +923245111848
- hammad173216@gmail.com
- ☐ https://github.com/Hammad400
- in linkedin.com/in/hammadmustafa400
- Postal Code:21230 ,Th:Balakot ,Dist:Mansehara,KPK,Pakistan

# **EDUCATION**

# **Bachelors in Computer Science**

Hazara Universty/GPGC Mansehara 2020 - 2024

#### Intermediate/HSSC/F.SC

BISE ATD/GPGC Mansehara 2017 - 2019

# CERTIFICATIONS

#### **Data Analysis with Python**

#### FreeCodeCamp.org

June 2021- August 2021

# Training on Data Science and Machine Learning

# Cybervision International/KP Digital Skills Initiative/UNDP

March 2021- August 2021

# Digital Marketing|Ecommerce

#### Digiskills.pk

May 2020- December 2020

# **HOBBIES**

- Book Reading
- Coding and Al
- NewsPaper Reading
- Exploring
- Business News Reading
- Social Media

# **Hammad Mustafa**

Seeking for Data Science | Machine Learning | Data Analytics position

# **PROFILE SUMMARY**

Hi, my name is Hammad Mustafa. I have one year experience in Data Science, Data Analytics and Machine Learning. I have completed more than 6 contracts on Fiverr and Upwork successfully with five stars feedback.

I am also writing blog posts at Medium.com and making videos at YouTube.com about data science to help people in learning emerging technologies.My First blog post achieved 1k views in one week.

I am Seeking for opportunities where I can utilize my analytical, mathematical, and technical skills to solve real life problems related to Business, Marketing and Health etc to draw insights that can help clients in business decisions.

# **WORK EXPERIENCE**

### Fiverr | Data Science Freelancer | April 2022- present

I have completed more than six contracts on fiverr about data analytics and machnine learning in python programming. I have earned more than 150 \$ on Fiverr.

### **Upwork** | Data Science Freelancer | June 2022- present

I have completed one contract of 70\$ on upwork about Gender,Age and Race detection from faces with deployment.

# The Sparks Foundation | Data Science Intern | Jan 2022- March 2022

This is remote internship of one month in which I have completed five data science and machine Learning projects .Major projects are super store sales analysis, Global Terrisium Analysis and Indian Premier League Sports Analysis

# **SKILLS**

Data Analytics
Machine Learning
Cloud & deployment
Python
SQL
Microsoft Excel

Microsoft PowerBI
Digital Marketing

# **OTHER LINKS**

- Medium: https://medium.com/@hammad173216
- Kaggle: <a href="https://www.kaggle.com/hammadmustafa400">https://www.kaggle.com/hammadmustafa400</a>
- YouTube Channel: <a href="https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCciHWr5l-g4LMoo6KnN5kCg">https://www.youtube.com/channel/UCciHWr5l-g4LMoo6KnN5kCg</a>
- GitHub: https://github.com/Hammad400/
- Note: To explore my projects please visit my personal website: https://hammad400.github.io/Hammad/